<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Daniel Jennings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Daniel Jennings</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:03:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Other Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/other-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:03:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/other-work/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer Work&#xA;Personal Tutor for Mathematics (2019 - 2024) Participant in the Climate Research Group Mona Climate Attribution and Modelling Workshop (June 2024) Assistant for Course Training in Discipleship and Ministry Programme - Artificial Intelligence and You (June 2024) Contribution to this platform, which is an outdated version of the work I currently do. (May 2021 - Dec 2021) Contribution to this paper, providing data visualizations. (May 2021 - Dec 2021) Lab Demonstrator at UWI Physics department For Dinthill Technical High School (Feb 2020) For Wolmer&amp;rsquo;s Boys High School (Feb 2019) Mentor for FortesHacks, Campion College&amp;rsquo;s first Hackathon (Jan 2020) Personal Tutor for Computer Science (Mar 2019 - May 2019) Volunteer for UWI Research Day (Mar 2019) Miscellaneous Work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work Personality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/work-personality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:49:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/work-personality/</guid>
      <description>Work Personality Profile&#xA;Tests and Strengths&#xA;Myers Briggs - ISTP Prefers explicit and practical advice and conversation Detail-oriented HEXACO Honesty-Humility - High Emotionality - Medium Extraversion - Medium Agreeableness - High Conscientiousness - High Openness - High Leadership Style - Democratic Focuses on building strengths and gaining consensus Good with constructive criticism Clifton StrengthsFinder - Strategic Thinking Absorbing and analyzing information for optimal team decisions Chronotype - Dolphin Best work between 9am-1pm Prefers structured environments Multi-potentialite Interdisciplinary, curious and cognitively flexible Prefers learning environment Weaknesses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Skills</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hard-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hard-skills/</guid>
      <description>Data and Programming Skills&#xA;Data Science and Scientific Computing Skills Data Cleaning and Manipulation e.g. Excel and Google Sheets Manipulation of Large Datasets Experience with Data Visualization tools e.g. Tableau and PowerBI Basic Proficiency with Databases and Data Management Systems e.g. MySQL Strong quantitivative skills Statistical knowledge and techniques Mathematical knowledge and techniques Predictive Analytics and Data Modelling Problem-solving and critical thinking abilities for problem identification Understanding of machine learning techniques and algorithms Data Proficiency - Entry, Collection, Cleaning and Presentation Data Verification and Quality Control Data-Driven Decision Making Program Testing and Debugging Programming Languages Python (Scripting, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Cartopy, Xarray, Scikit-Learn, Scipy, Jupyter Notebook, Pycharm) HTML/CSS R C (Basic proficiency) Git (Basic Proficiency) Node (Basic Proficiency) Linux (Basic Proficiency) Javascript (Basic Proficiency) Program Testing and Debugging SWOT analysis Web analytics Programs/Software Related</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Skills</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/soft-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:41:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/soft-skills/</guid>
      <description>Problem-solving&#xA;Critical thinking Analysis Lateral thinking/Creativity Logical Reasoning Persistence Observation Brainstorming Planning Goal-setting Evaluation Deductive Reasoning Strategic thinking Work ethic&#xA;Discipline Integrity Responsibility Initiative Self-awareness Commitment Professionalism Organization&#xA;Attention to detail Record keeping Analytical thinking Perceptiveness Proactivity Communication&#xA;Mutual respect Active listening Verbal communication Written communication Constructive feedback Friendliness Awareness Open-mindedness Teamwork&#xA;Conflict management Listening Collaboration Mediation Idea Exchange Cooperation Coordination Encouragement Adaptability&#xA;Flexibility Curiosity Growth Mindset Self-management Optimism Resilience Quick learning Reliability Interpersonal Skills</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
